http://www.americanbaptistfdn.org/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
American Baptist Fdn
Online Payday Loans Guide
TweetEmail
TweetEmailIf you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at info@americanbaptistfdn.org.
At www.americanbaptistfdn.org, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.americanbaptistfdn.org and how it is used.
Log Files
Like many other Web sites, www.americanbaptistfdn.org makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.
Cookies and Web Beacons
www.americanbaptistfdn.org does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.
DoubleClick DART Cookie
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.americanbaptistfdn.org.
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to www.americanbaptistfdn.org and other sites on the Internet.
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include ….
Google Adsense
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.americanbaptistfdn.org send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.
www.americanbaptistfdn.org has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.americanbaptistfdn.org’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
Related Posts:PayDay Loans OnlineHow to Choose the Right Payday Loan Lender?Do I Need Security To Take Out A Personal Loan?Online Payday Loans with No Credit CheckCan I Get a Payday Loan on My Prepaid Card?Payday Loan Companies to the Rescue when Credit Runs Out
Search
Search for:
Featured Video
PagesHome
About Us
Payday Loans
Contact Us
Privacy Policy
Recent Posts
PayDay Loans Online
What happens if I can’t repay my payday loan?
Can I Get a Payday Loan on My Prepaid Card?
How to Choose the Right Payday Loan Lender?
Do I Need Security To Take Out A Personal Loan?
Featured Product
Useful LinksA DAD-OF-THREE who ended up owing £4,645 to doorstep lenders claims
The Truth About Money and Mental Illness in 3 Minutes
NCUA wants to expand payday lending alternatives for credit unions, consumers
Payday LoansShoppers grab last-minute items before new Alberta restrictions... - Todayville.comROI Rocket: US Households Under Increasing Stress From Pandemic Surge And Related Financial Hardships - StreetInsider.comThis is the amount of savings you need to increase housing security and avoid debt, study finds - CNBCMore Canadians curious about taking high-interest loans against their cars - Automotive News CanadaMartin Lewis calls for 'explosive' buy now pay later market to be regulated at 'maximum speed' - MoneySavingExpertCoronavirus: Quarter of Brits to cut back at Christmas with London most-affected - Yahoo Finance UKHow much money should you keep in savings? - FOX 6 MilwaukeeThis Delaware financial advocacy group wants to expand banking services for the low-income with grant - The News JournalFinancial regulators take another step toward payday lending database adoption, months after deadline - The Nevada IndependentAlberta premier to speak on COVID-19 after latest restrictions... - Todayville.com
